{
    "id": "d46110f0c3314099a3b2febc1e1c7c0b",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I am thinking of changing ……………………",
            "description": "When we talk about changing one thing for another, we often use change with a plural object.",
            "answers": [
                "job",
                "jobs",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t …………………….. whether I lose – I am happy with what I have achieved.",
            "description": "Care is used without about before a conjunction. ",
            "answers": [
                "care",
                "care about",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t ………………………… the result.",
            "description": "Before an object, we use care about.",
            "answers": [
                "care",
                "care about",
                "care for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t take more than 5 minutes to ………………………… ready.",
            "description": "We do not use become to talk about deliberate actions.",
            "answers": [
                "get",
                "become",
                "turn"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The village ……………………….. I live is not far from the town.",
            "description": "\r\nThat can be used instead of which or whom. But it cannot be used instead of when or where.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "where",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "His recovery seemed …………………………",
            "description": "After copular verbs, we use adjectives, not adverbs.",
            "answers": [
                "impossible",
                "impossibly",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I have bought …………………………..",
            "description": "Some uncountable nouns are plural and do not have singular forms. Groceries is an example.",
            "answers": [
                "the grocery",
                "a grocery",
                "the groceries"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The new job is not much different ………………………… the old one.",
            "description": "From is generally used after different. In British English, to is also possible and in American English than is common.",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "than",
                "to",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "I doubt ……………………….. she will come this evening.",
            "description": "We can use if, whether or that to introduce the clauses after the verb doubt.",
            "answers": [
                "whether",
                "if",
                "that",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "His success was ……………………….. his teacher.",
            "description": "We can use due to after ‘be’. Owing to is not usually used like that.",
            "answers": [
                "due to",
                "owing to",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "If you are not satisfied with their hospitality, you can go …………………………….",
            "description": "Elsewhere means the same as somewhere else. It is slightly more formal. ",
            "answers": [
                "elsewhere",
                "somewhere else",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She takes ………………………. trouble over her work.",
            "description": "Especial is not normally used as an adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "special",
                "especial",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}